Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Boss,
رئيس،
this is the couple I told you about.
هذا هو الزوجان الذي أخبرتك عنهما.
Their cooking skills are exceptional,
مهاراتهم في الطبخ استثنائية،
definitely better than anyone in our troupe.
بالتأكيد أفضل من أي شخص في فرقتنا.
Perfect appearance, aroma, and taste.
مظهر ورائحة وطعم مثاليين.
Well then,
حسنا إذن،
stay and help us for a couple of days.
ابقى وساعدنا لبضعة أيام.
Thank you, boss.
شكرا لك يا رئيس.
There's a side room in the back yard.
هناك غرفة جانبية في الفناء الخلفي.
You two can stay there,
يمكنكم البقاء هناك
so you'll be available whenever needed.
لذا ستكون متاحًا عند الحاجة إليك.
We'll definitely be at your service.
سوف نكون في خدمتكم بالتأكيد.
Brother-in-law,
شقيق الزوج،
drink up!
اشرب!
Ha ha ha!
هاهاهاها!
Well, I must say,
حسنا، يجب أن أقول،
Jiulang's performance today
أداء جيولانغ اليوم
is more flavorful than usual.
أكثر نكهة من المعتاد.
Look at that!
أنظر إلى ذلك!
As expected of Master Mei,
كما هو متوقع من المعلمة مي،
his singing skills have improved again.
لقد تحسنت مهاراته الغنائية مرة أخرى.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
This Mei Jiulang
هذا مي جيولانج
seems different from what we saw before.
يبدو مختلفًا عما رأيناه من قبل.
Excellent!
ممتاز!
Bravo!
برافو!
Good!
جيد!
Reward him!
كافئه!
Give him a generous reward!
أعطيه مكافأة سخية!
Today's performance,
أداء اليوم،
though performed by Master Mei,
على الرغم من أدائها من قبل المعلم مي،
has more charm than usual.
لديه سحر أكثر من المعتاد.
Don't you all agree?
ألا تتفقون جميعا؟
Indeed.
بالفعل.
This is Mei Jiulang's room.
هذه غرفة مي جيولانغ.
It's so tidy.
إنه مرتب للغاية.
Does he have OCD or something?
هل يعاني من اضطراب الوسواس القهري أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Today,
اليوم،
didn't Mei Jiulang ask Su Huasheng to buy rouge?
ألم تطلب Mei Jiulang من Su Huasheng شراء اللون الأحمر؟
He got scolded for it too.
لقد تعرض للتوبيخ بسبب ذلك أيضًا.
Is this it?
هل هذا هو؟
Should be.
ينبغي أن يكون.
Mei Jiulang brought it back and used it.
أعادها مي جيولانغ واستخدمها.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This is for women.
هذا للنساء.
Try it.
جربها.
See how it feels.
انظر كيف تشعر.
That'll cost you extra.
سيكلفك هذا مبلغا إضافيا.
You actually look quite cute like this.
أنت تبدو لطيفًا جدًا بهذا الشكل.
But when you speak, you sound like a demon.
ولكن عندما تتحدث، يبدو صوتك مثل الشيطان.
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر فيه؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It smells terrible.
رائحتها فظيعة.
Like lard.
مثل شحم الخنزير.
Apart from his voice issues,
بصرف النظر عن مشاكل صوته،
a famous actor like Mei Jiulang
ممثل مشهور مثل مي جيولانغ
would be extremely particular about his makeup products.
سيكون شديد الاهتمام بمنتجات المكياج التي يقدمها.
He wouldn't casually use inferior products.
لن يستخدم منتجات رديئة الجودة بشكل عرضي.
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Someone is impersonating Mei Jiulang.
شخص ما ينتحل شخصية مي جيولانغ.
This teacup and the teapot in the kitchen are clearly a set.
من الواضح أن فنجان الشاي وإبريق الشاي الموجودين في المطبخ يشكلان مجموعة واحدة.
They must be exclusively for Mei Jiulang's use.
يجب أن تكون مخصصة لاستخدام Mei Jiulang حصريًا.
Could someone
هل يمكن لشخص ما
be trying to prevent Mei Jiulang from performing tonight?
هل تحاول منع مي جيولانغ من الأداء الليلة؟
They intended to tamper with the teapot,
كانوا يعتزمون العبث بإبريق الشاي،
but unexpectedly,
ولكن بشكل غير متوقع،
we accidentally broke it.
لقد كسرناها عن طريق الخطأ.
Who exactly is trying to stop
من الذي يحاول التوقف بالضبط؟
Mei Jiulang from performing tonight?
هل سيتمكن مي جيولانغ من الأداء الليلة؟
Master Jiu,
سيد جيو,
you're back.
لقد عدت.
Look at you trembling.
أنظر إليك ترتجف.
What are you afraid of?
ماذا تخاف منه؟
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
I'll protect your life.
سأحمي حياتك.
I'm nervous.
أنا متوترة.
Finally.
أخيراً.
Finally my turn to sit here.
وأخيرا جاء دوري للجلوس هنا.
Haha!
هاها!
Senior.
كبير.
It's actually him.
إنه هو في الواقع.
Those people sitting down there watching the show today,
هؤلاء الأشخاص الذين يجلسون هناك ويشاهدون العرض اليوم،
they claim to be your fans.
يزعمون أنهم معجبين بك.
Haha!
هاها!
I spit on that!
أنا أبصق على ذلك!
I deliberately misplaced my beauty mark today.
لقد أضعت علامة جمالي عمدًا اليوم.
Not a single person noticed.
ولم يلاحظ أحد ذلك.
Their love for you is all fake.
حبهم لك كله مزيف.
Haha!
هاها!
What is Su Huasheng up to?
ماذا يفعل سو هوا شنغ؟
Where is Mei Jiulang?
أين مي جيولانغ؟
Am I not
هل انا لست كذلك
your most devoted fan?
من هو المعجب الأكثر إخلاصًا لك؟
It wasn't in vain that I spent
لم يكن عبثا أن أمضيت
day and night imitating your singing style.
ليلاً ونهاراً يقلد أسلوبك الغنائي.
This day
هذا اليوم
has finally come in handy.
لقد أصبح الأمر مفيدًا أخيرًا.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
Senior.
كبير.
Today,
اليوم،
all the audience members were saying...
وكان جميع الحضور يقولون...
They said
قالوا
Jiulang seems to sing better than before.
يبدو أن جيولانغ يغني بشكل أفضل من ذي قبل.
Did you hear that?
هل سمعت ذلك؟
Ten times better than you.
أفضل منك بعشر مرات.
No, not ten times.
لا، ليس عشر مرات.
A hundred times better!
أفضل مائة مرة!
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Jiulang.
جيولانغ.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Hehe.
هاها.
It's the troupe master.
إنه قائد الفرقة.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Jiulang.
جيولانغ.
Today
اليوم
the Minister is in a good mood.
الوزير في مزاج جيد.
He says tonight
يقول الليلة
he wants to invite you
يريد دعوتك
to perform at his mansion again.
لأداء عروضه في قصره مرة أخرى.
He also says
ويقول أيضا
it's only been a few days
لقد مرت بضعة أيام فقط
but your singing skills have improved considerably.
لكن مهاراتك الغنائية تحسنت بشكل كبير.
The Minister really misses you.
إن الوزير يفتقدك حقًا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Get ready early.
استعد مبكرًا.
A carriage from his mansion will pick you up tonight.
ستأتيك عربة من قصره الليلة.
You'll certainly get your share of the reward.
سوف تحصل بالتأكيد على نصيبك من المكافأة.
Sing well.
غنِّ جيداً.
Don't ruin our Ruichun Garden's reputation
لا تفسدوا سمعة حديقة رويتشون الخاصة بنا
or your own name.
أو اسمك الخاص.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't ruin our reputation.
لن أفسد سمعتنا.
You can see how much they love me.
يمكنك أن ترى كم يحبونني.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I need to get ready now.
أنا بحاجة إلى الاستعداد الآن.
What is Su Huasheng up to?
ماذا يفعل سو هوا شنغ؟
Let's follow him and see.
دعونا نتبعه ونرى.
Boss, my leg is numb.
يا رئيس، رجلي مخدرة.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Boss.
رئيس.
Follow him.
اتبعه.
It's an ice cellar.
إنه قبو جليدي.
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
Let's go down and take a look.
دعونا ننزل ونلقي نظرة.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
It's too high.
إنه مرتفع للغاية.
Fear of heights?
الخوف من المرتفعات؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Hold on to me.
تمسك بي.
Holding tight.
تمسك بقوة.
We're here.
نحن هنا.